Tufts Combined Catalogs, Bulletins, and Course Announcements UP005
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Combined Catalogs, Bulletins, and Course Announcements
1854 -- 1970
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
Trustees of Tufts College
UP005
70 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the bound Catalogs, Bulletins, and Course Announcements from 1856 to 1970 of Tufts College. In 1956, the bulletin changed name to reflect Tufts University and the individual schools. Volumes include school descriptions, degree requirements, course descriptions, and entrance requirements. Early volumes include the roster of trustees, faculty, staff, and enrolled students. After 1970, individual school bulletins were no longer bound together.
DCA is missing the catalog for the 1918-1919 academic year; it may never have been printed.
Biographical / Historical
In 1851, a Board of Trustees was nominated by the subscribers to replace the temporary Board created at the 1847 Educational Convention of the Universalist Church. The new Board selected a site and drew up the governing rules for the new College.
- Complete and Combined Catalogs, 1854 -- 1970; UP005.001; 70 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the bound Catalogs, Bulletins, and Course Announcements from 1856 to 1970 of Tufts College. In 1956, the bulletin changed name to reflect Tufts University and the individual schools. Volumes include school descriptions, degree requirements, course descriptions, and entrance requirements. Early volumes include the roster of trustees, faculty, staff, and enrolled students. After 1970, individual school bulletins were no longer bound together.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Catalogue of the Trustees & Officers of Tufts College, 1854 -- 1876; UP005.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - Catalogue of the Officers and Students of Tufts College, 1877 -- 1891; UP005.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1891 -- 1898; UP005.001.003.00001 (Box Volume 3)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1898 -- 1901; UP005.001.004.00001 (Box Volume 4)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1901 -- 1902; UP005.001.005.00001 (Box Volume 5)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1902 -- 1903; UP005.001.006.00001 (Box Volume 6)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1903 -- 1904; UP005.001.007.00001 (Box Volume 7)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1904 -- 1905; UP005.001.008.00001 (Box Volume 8)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1905 -- 1906; UP005.001.009.00001 (Box Volume 9)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1906 -- 1907; UP005.001.010.00001 (Box Volume 10)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1907 -- 1908; UP005.001.011.00001 (Box Volume 11)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1908 -- 1909; UP005.001.012.00001 (Box Volume 12)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1909 -- 1910; UP005.001.013.00001 (Box Volume 13)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1910 -- 1911; UP005.001.014.00001 (Box Volume 14)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1911 -- 1912; UP005.001.015.00001 (Box Volume 15)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1912 -- 1913; UP005.001.016.00001 (Box Volume 16)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1913 -- 1914; UP005.001.017.00001 (Box Volume 17)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1914 -- 1915; UP005.001.018.00001 (Box Volume 18)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1915 -- 1916; UP005.001.019.00001 (Box Volume 19)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1916 -- 1917; UP005.001.020.00001 (Box Volume 20)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1917 -- 1918; UP005.001.021.00001 (Box Volume 21)
  - Announcement of the Two-Year Pre-Medical Course, 1918 -- 1919; UP005.001.022.00001 (Box Volume 22)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1919 -- 1920; UP005.001.023.00001 (Box Volume 23)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1920 -- 1921; UP005.001.024.00001 (Box Volume 24)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1921 -- 1922; UP005.001.025.00001 (Box Volume 25)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1922 -- 1923; UP005.001.026.00001 (Box Volume 26)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1923 -- 1924; UP005.001.027.00001 (Box Volume 27)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1924 -- 1925; UP005.001.028.00001 (Box Volume 28)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1925 -- 1926; UP005.001.029.00001 (Box Volume 29)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1926 -- 1927; UP005.001.030.00001 (Box Volume 30)
  - Catalogue of Tufts College, 1927 -- 1928; UP005.001.031.00001 (Box Volume 31)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1928 -- 1929; UP005.001.032.00001 (Box Volume 32)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1929 -- 1930; UP005.001.033.00001 (Box Volume 33)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1930 -- 1931; UP005.001.034.00001 (Box Volume 34)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1931 -- 1932; UP005.001.035.00001 (Box Volume 35)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1932 -- 1933; UP005.001.036.00001 (Box Volume 36)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1933 -- 1934; UP005.001.037.00001 (Box Volume 37)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1934 -- 1935; UP005.001.038.00001 (Box Volume 38)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1935 -- 1936; UP005.001.039.00001 (Box Volume 39)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1936 -- 1937; UP005.001.040.00001 (Box Volume 40)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1937 -- 1938; UP005.001.041.00001 (Box Volume 41)
  - Catalogue Number of Tufts College Bulletin, 1938 -- 1939; UP005.001.042.00001 (Box Volume 42)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1939 -- 1940; UP005.001.043.00001 (Box Volume 43)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1940 -- 1941; UP005.001.044.00001 (Box Volume 44)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1941 -- 1942; UP005.001.045.00001 (Box data_value_missing_4111f71f35973f726631d79399f11b27)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1942 -- 1943; UP005.001.046.00001 (Box data_value_missing_4111f71f35973f726631d79399f11b27)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1943 -- 1944; UP005.001.047.00001 (Box Volume 47)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1944 -- 1945; UP005.001.048.00001 (Box Volume 48)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1945 -- 1946; UP005.001.049.00001 (Box Volume 49)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1946 -- 1947; UP005.001.050.00001 (Box Volume 50)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1947 -- 1948; UP005.001.051.00001 (Box Volume 51)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1948 -- 1949; UP005.001.052.00001 (Box Volume 52)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1949 -- 1950; UP005.001.053.00001 (Box Volume 53)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue, 1950 -- 1951; UP005.001.054.00001 (Box Volume 54)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue Number, 1951 -- 1952; UP005.001.055.00001 (Box Volume 55)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue Number, 1952 -- 1953; UP005.001.056.00001 (Box Volume 56)
  - Bulletin of Tufts College: Complete Catalogue Number, 1953 -- 1954; UP005.001.057.00001 (Box Volume 57)
  - Tufts University Bulletin: Complete Catalogue, 1954 -- 1955; UP005.001.058.00001 (Box Volume 58)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Complete Catalogue, 1955 -- 1956; UP005.001.059.00001 (Box Volume 59)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1956 -- 1957; UP005.001.060.00001 (Box Volume 60)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1957 -- 1958; UP005.001.061.00001 (Box Volume 61)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1958 -- 1959; UP005.001.062.00001 (Box Volume 62)
  - Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1959 -- 1960; UP005.001.063.00001 (Box Volume 63)
  - Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1960 -- 1961; UP005.001.064.00001 (Box Volume 64)
  - Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1961 -- 1963; UP005.001.065.00001 (Box Volume 65)
  - Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1963 -- 1964; UP005.001.066.00001 (Box Volume 66)
  - Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1964 -- 1966; UP005.001.067.00001 (Box Volume 67)
    Additional copy of 1965-1966 in reading room.
  - Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1966 -- 1967; UP005.001.068.00001 (Box Volume 68)
  - Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1967 -- 1968; UP005.001.069.00001 (Box Volume 69)
  - Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1968 -- 1969; UP005.001.070.00001 (Box Volume 70)
  - Combined Bulletins of the Colleges and Schools, 1970; UP005.001.071.00001 (Box Volume 71)